全世界有超过 15 亿人经常使用 Snapchat、TikTok、Instagram Stories 和其他智能手机应用程序观看 60 秒或更短的短视频，其中一半以上的人年龄在 24 岁以下。
More than 1.5 billion people around the world, over half of them under the age of 24, regularly watch short videos, clips of 60 seconds or less, using Snapchat, TikTok, Instagram Stories, and other smartphone apps.
七年前，这个市场几乎不存在。
The market barely existed seven years ago.
然而，如今创作者每天上传的短视频数量已达 7.02 亿条。
Yet today, creators are uploading 702 million short videos every day.
由于我们的注意力正在下降到几秒钟，短视频不仅会继续存在，而且会成为新常态。
As our attention span is falling to seconds, short video is not only here to stay, but will become the new normal.
与 Instagram 等其他社交平台不同的是，在这些平台上，完美剪辑、精雕细琢的图片是常态，而短视频则更容易让人接受，吸引着不完美和真实的人。
Unlike other social platforms such as Instagram, where perfectly edited, polished images are the norm, short videos are more accessible, inviting imperfection and authenticity.
由于每个片段的时间都很短，内容制作者必须具有创造性和简洁的沟通能力。
And because each clip is so short, content producers have to be creative and concise communicators.
但是，这些短小精悍的视频不仅仅是好玩和娱乐。
But these bite-sized videos are more than just fun and entertainment.
就我个人而言，作为一名顾问和母亲，短视频是我获取育儿技巧的途径。
For me personally, as a consultant and mother, short videos are where I get parenting tips.
在上班途中，我可以很快了解到旅行中母乳喂养的秘诀，并获得如何让女儿早日入睡的好点子。
On my way to work, I can quickly learn about the secrets of breastfeeding while traveling and get great ideas about how to make my daughter sleep sooner.
企业也认识到，短视频是寻找新客户和扩大受众多样性的好方法。
Businesses are also learning that short videos is a great way to find new customers and expand the diversity of the audiences.
今年早些时候，我与世界领先的短视频平台 TikTok 共同领导了一个项目，评估这种 "一口式 "经济对经济和社会的影响。
Earlier this year, I led a project with TikTok, the world's leading short video platform, to assess the economic and social impact of this bite-sized economy.
我们的研究表明，这一年轻媒体正在改变的不仅仅是我们消磨闲暇时间的方式。
Our study shows that this young medium is changing a lot more than the way we spend our leisure time.
2019 年，短视频产生的商品和服务销售额约为 950 亿美元，在全球范围内创造了约 120 万个就业岗位。
In 2019, short video generated an estimated 95 billion US dollars in goods and services sold and created roughly 1.2 million jobs globally.
即使在如此短的生命周期内，短视频也已经在影响着我们的工作、交流和学习方式。
Even within this short lifespan, short video is already impacting the way we work, communicate and learn.
在 "COVID-19 "时代，当世界各地的博物馆面临无限期关闭时，许多博物馆已迅速行动起来，以远程方式吸引新的、更年轻的观众。
In the age of COVID-19, while museums around the world are facing indefinite closure, many have acted quickly to bring in and engage a new, younger audience remotely.
佛罗伦萨的乌菲兹美术馆在三年前刚刚建立了自己的新腾博会官方网站，它正在利用短视频吸引新的观众来欣赏自己的雕像和绘画作品。
The Uffizi Gallery in Florence, which just established its official new website three years ago, is using short video to attract new audiences to their statues and paintings.
通过将展品与表情符号、音乐歌词或有趣的引语相搭配，博物馆使其艺术品更容易被年轻一代的艺术爱好者所接受，也更贴近他们的生活。
By matching exhibits with emojis, music lyrics, or funny quotes, the museum is making its artwork more accessible and relevant to the young generation of art lovers.
在它最近发布的一个帖子中，一个卡通冠状病毒变成了一块石头，在卡拉瓦乔的画作《美杜莎》前被砸成两半。
In one of its recent posts, a cartoon coronavirus turned into a rock and smashed in half in front of Caravaggio's painting Medusa, who has the power to turn those who gaze at her into stone.
冠状病毒
Coronavirus!
乌菲兹还尝试让有影响力的人在短视频平台上直播画廊，让世界各地的观众体验他们从未亲眼见到过的艺术。
Uffizi also experimented with influencers live streaming from the gallery on short video platform, allowing viewers around the world to experience art that they've never been able to see in person.
自 2020 年 4 月出现在 TikTok 上以来。
since its appearance on TikTok in April 2020.
博物馆的个人主页在三个月内吸引了 43 000 多名粉丝。
The museum's profile has attracted more than 43,000 followers in three months.
这一速度远远快于他们在 Twitter 上的发展历程，在过去四年中，他们在 Twitter 上建立了类似数量的粉丝群。
The speed is far quicker than their journey on Twitter, where it built up similar number of fan base using the past four years.
小企业也在利用短视频寻找新的受众，这些受众可能从未听说过他们或他们的产品。
Small businesses are also using short video as a way to find new audiences who might have never heard of them or their products before.
2018 年，中国领先的短视频平台豆瓣作为其中国扶贫社会责任倡议的一部分，发起了帮助中国山区个体农户和小企业销售农产品的活动。
In 2018, Douyin, the leading Chinese short video platform, as part of its social responsibility initiative to alleviate poverty in China, launched a campaign to help individual farmers and small businesses in China's mountainous areas sell farm produce.
作为试点项目之一，豆瓣邀请内容生产者制作四段 15 秒的短视频，展示其产品的品质。
As one of its pilot projects, Douyin invited content producers to create four pieces of 15-second short videos, showcasing the quality of their products.
这是其他常规公关活动（如宣传文章）的补充。
This is on top of other regular PR initiatives such as promotional articles.
豆瓣希望利用短视频的庞大用户群，找到那些可能对这些产品感兴趣的客户，然后将他们与电子商务网站连接起来，让人们可以边看视频边买东西。
Douyin wanted to leverage the large user base of short video to find those customers who might be interested in those products and then connected them with the e-commerce website so that people can buy things as they watch the videos.
在短短五天内，该倡议帮助四川省近 4000 个家庭售出了 12 万公斤李子。
In just five days, the initiative helped nearly 4,000 families in Sichuan province sell an astonishing 120,000 kilograms of plums.
许多有意雇用和招募年轻人的品牌都将短视频作为与 Z 世代互动的新方式。例如，麦当劳一半以上的员工年龄在 16-24 岁之间。
Many brands that are interested in hiring and recruiting young people have been using short video as a fresh way to engage with Generation Z. For example, more than half of McDonald's employees are aged between 16 to 24.
在澳大利亚，该品牌近年来一直在努力招募员工。
In Australia, the brand was struggling to recruit in recent years.
于是，麦当劳推出了一款名为 "Snaplication "的 Snapchat 镜头，让用户拍摄 10 秒钟的视频，解释自己为什么会成为麦当劳的完美员工，然后提示他们进入职位申请链接。
So it launched something called Snaplication, which is a Snapchat lens that enabled users to shoot 10 second videos explaining why they'd be a perfect McDonald's employee and then prompt them to the link of job application.
在发起活动后的 24 小时内，麦当劳收到了 3000 份 Snaplications。
Within 24 hours after launching the campaign, McDonald's received 3000 Snaplications.
是他们使用传统方法整周收到的数量的四倍。
four times more than the number they received in the whole week using traditional methods.
目前还不清楚通过短视频招聘是否是找到合适人选或留住人才的最佳方式。
Well, it's unclear whether hiring over short video as the best way to find the right people for the job or to retain talent.
但仅从招募人数来看，这项活动在全球范围内都很受欢迎。
But judging solely from recruiting numbers, the campaign was a global hit.
在沙特阿拉伯，麦当劳在 24 小时内收到了 43,000 份申请。
In Saudi Arabia, McDonald's received 43,000 applications within 24 hours.
随后，该公司在美国再次发起了这一活动。
and the company launched the campaign again later in the US.
就像我喜欢从短视频中获取育儿技巧一样，许多用户也希望利用这个平台来学习，不过是小剂量的学习。
Much like how I like to get parenting tips from short video, many users also want to leverage the platform to learn, but in tiny bite-sized doses.
在我们的研究中，全球短视频用户将发现新兴趣和学习新技能列为平台的最大益处。
In our study, short video users globally ranked the top benefits of the platform as discovering new interests and learning new skills.
特别是在新兴市场，用于学习和教育的短视频具有改变现状的巨大潜力。
In emerging market especially, short video for learning and education has huge potential to change the status quo.
2019 年，TikTok 在印度发起了一项活动，旨在使印度数字社区的学习民主化。
In 2019, TikTok launched a campaign in India with the aim of democratizing learning for the Indian digital community.
虽然该应用自 2020 年 7 月起在国内被禁，但它却引发了对教育短视频内容的巨大需求，其他平台也纷纷加入进来，填补这一空白。
While the app has been banned in the country since July 2020, it launched a huge demand for educational short video content, and other platforms are jumping in to fill in the space.
TikTok 通过与印度社会企业、教育初创企业和热门创作者合作，制作了 15 秒的短视频，涵盖了从学校科学到学习新语言等一系列主题，从而引发了这一趋势。
TikTok was able to spark this trend by collaborating with Indian social enterprises, education startups, and popular creators to produce 15-second short videos that cover a range of topics, from school-level science to learning new languages.
随着第一波短视频在该平台上广泛传播，受众受到了启发，有些人甚至开始制作自己的教育内容。
As the first wave of short video became widely spread on the platform, audiences got inspired, and some even began to create their own educational content.
截至 2019 年 10 月，该活动已产生了超过 1000 万个视频，获得了 480 亿次观看。
By October 2019, the campaign had generated more than 10 million videos and garnered 48 billion views.
通过帮助人们学习和参与内容创作过程，短视频实际上正在帮助培养和培训能够应对未来挑战的技术人才。
Through helping people learn and participate into the process of content creation, short videos are in fact helping prep and train the skilled population that can take on the challenges of the future.
与所有社交媒体一样，人们对短视频平台的担忧也不无道理。
Like all social media, there are valid concerns around short video platforms.
包括数据隐私、格式的成瘾性以及内容缺乏细微差别和上下文。
including data privacy, the addictive nature of the format, and the lack of nuance and context in the content.
不过，我仍然认为，短视频的积极成果将大于其弊端。
However, I still think that the positive outcomes of short video will outweigh its downsides.
我相信，未来短视频将成为一股更加重要的经济和社会力量。
I believe short video will become a more vital economic and social force in the future.
正因为如此，我们需要通过用户、平台和政策制定者之间的合作，找到从这一年轻媒体中获益的正确方式。
It is precisely because of this that we need to find the right way to benefit from this young medium through collaboration among users, platforms, and policymakers.
谢谢。
Thank you.